[
    {
        "question": "Aphantasia is a condition, which describes people, for whom it is hard to visualise mental images.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Niel Kenmuir was unable to count sheep in his head",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "People with aphantasia struggle to remember personal traits and clothes of different people.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "NOT GIVEN",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Niel regrets that he cannot portray an image of his fiancee in his mind.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Inability to picture things in someone's head is often a cause of distress for a person",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "All people with aphantasia start to feel 'isolated' or 'alone' at some point of their lives.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "NOT GIVEN",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Lauren Beard's career depends on her imagination.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The author met Lauren Beard when she was working on a comedy scene in her next book.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": " Only a small fraction of people have imagination as ___________ as Lauren does.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Vibrant",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Hyperphantasia is ___________ to aphantasia.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Polar-opposite",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "There are a lot of subjectivity in comparing people's imagination - somebody's vivid scene could be another person's ___________.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Grainy picture",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Prof Zeman is ___________ that aphantasia is not an illness.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Adamant",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Many people spend their lives with ___________ somewhere in the mind's eye.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Imagery hovering",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Jailbreak with creative thinking _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Five common traits among rule-breakers _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "G",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Comparison between criminals and traditional businessmen _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Can drug baron's espace teach legitimate corporations? _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Great entrepreneur _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "H",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "How criminal groups deceive the law _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The difference between legal and illegal organisations _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Similarity between criminals and start-up founders _____.",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H"],
        "correct_answer": "F",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "To escape from a prison, Joaquin Guzman had to use such traits as creative thinking, long-term planning and _____ .",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Perseverance",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The Sinaloa cartel built a grand underground tunnel and even used a _____ to avoid the fence.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Catapult",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The main difference between two groups is that criminals, unlike large corporations, often have _____ encoded into their daily life.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Improvisation",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Due to being persuasive, Walid Abdul-Wahab found a _____ of Amish camel milk farmers.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Network",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The main goal of this article is to: ",
        "answers": ["Show different ways of illegal activity", "Give an overview of various criminals and their gangs", "Draw a comparison between legal and illegal business, providing examples", "Justify criminals with creative thinking"],
        "correct_answer": "Draw a comparison between legal and illegal business, providing examples",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Armando Iannucci expressed a need of having more popular channels.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "John Whittingdale wanted to dismantle the BBC.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Iannucci delivered the 30th annual MacTaggart Lecture.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "NOT GIVEN",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Iannucci believes that British television has contributed to the success of American TV-shows.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "There have been negotiations over the future of the BBC in July.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {   
        "question": "Iannucci praised everything EXCEPT",
        "answers": ["US shows", "British shows", "Corporation", "British programming"],
        "correct_answer": "US shows",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "To advise on the charter renewal Mr Whittingdale appointed a panel of",
        "answers": ["five people", "two people", "seven people", "four people"],
        "correct_answer": "seven people",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who of these people was NOT invited to the discussion concerning BBC renewal?",
        "answers": ["Armando Iannucci", "Dawn Airey", "John Whittingdale", "Stewart Purvis"],
        "correct_answer": "Armando Iannucci",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "There panel of experts lacks:",
        "answers": ["media owners", "people who make enduring TV-shows", "gurus of Television industry", "top executives"],
        "correct_answer": "people who make enduring TV-shows",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Conducted poll in December says that most Americans are __________ with the way that things are going.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Angry",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Many people are angrier than a year ago, particulary __________.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Republicans",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The economical rates are decreasing, even though the country has recovered from the __________.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Recession",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Billionaires and immigrants are the two sides of one political __________.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Coin",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "It is expected that the __________ will be the biggest ethnic group to move in the USA by the year 2055.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Asians",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "It has been an era of demographic, racial, cultural, religious and __________ change.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Generational",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Roberto Suro says that migrants might become a __________ of anger.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Target",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Six to ten Americans believe that government has too much __________.",
        "answers": [],
        "correct_answer": "Power",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The Congress has more responsibilities now than in 1970s.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "William Galston believes that the appeal of Donald Trump and Bernie Sanders is growing bigger each day.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "NOT GIVEN",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ted Cruz is running as an anti-establishment candidate.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The number of Americans who think that the US \"stands above all other countries in the world\" increased by 10% in 2014 compared to 2012.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Since 9/11 there's been a feeling of war in America and it's still here.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The Americans had the same reaction to the San Bernardino shooting as French to the Paris attacks.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The ideological diversity between the Democrats and the Republicans is stronger than ever now.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The pragmatic mass consists of a lot of young people.",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 1,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Possible damage _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "D",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Shocking news _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "A",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Mix of different studies _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "F",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Misleading information _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "C",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Types of e-cigarettes _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "E",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "A place where the controversial research was written _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"], 
        "correct_answer": "B",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The defence of the article _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "I",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "A research by an e-cigarette industry _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "H",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The consistent evidence _____",
        "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D", "E", "F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "correct_answer": "G",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "New controversial research suggests that e-cigarettes _____",
        "answers": ["make it easier to quit smoking", "make it harder to quit smoking", "don't play a major role in quitting smoking", "the research doen't answer this question"],
        "correct_answer": "make it harder to quit smoking",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ann McNeill critisized the research because _____",
        "answers": ["the majority of other researches disagree with this review", "the definition of e-cigarettes is a bit loose", "some information is either inaccurate or misleading", "the analysis mashed together some very different studies"],
        "correct_answer": "some information is either inaccurate or misleading", 
        "part": 2, 
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "This article aims at _____",
        "answers": ["finding the truth about e-cigarettes, providing facts", "showing that the e-cigarettes are worthless", "promoting the use of e-cigarettes", "analyzing different scientific researches"],
        "correct_answer": "finding the truth about e-cigarettes, providing facts",
        "part": 2,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Called a debate on the issue _____", 
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Nobody from the above",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Launched the petition _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Stevie Wise",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "States that women are willing to pay more _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Mark Billige",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Says that women are more careful shoppers than men _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Nobody from the above",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Says that companies should keep in mind gender equality while making products _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Jemima Olchawski",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Was told that there are many problems with prices, especially with toys and clothes _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Stevie Wise",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "States that women are getting ripped off twice _____",
        "answers": ["Stevie Wise", "Mark Billige", "Jemima Olchawski", "Nobody from the above"],
        "correct_answer": "Jemima Olchawski",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Pink tax means that women are being charged more than men for the same products _____",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Due to the fact that the petition gathered more than 43,000 signatures the issue has been raised in Parliament _____",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "NOT GIVEN",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "After comparing the prices of 800 products., it was concluded that women's versions were 7% more expensive than men's _____",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "It is hard for the retailers to pretend that the gender price gap is an innocent mistake _____",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "FALSE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "If male and female products are situated in different sections, it makes it harder to examine the prices _____",
        "answers": ["TRUE", "FALSE", "NOT GIVEN"],
        "correct_answer": "TRUE",
        "part": 3,
        "test_type": "reading",
        "test_id": 2
    }
]